import { Question } from "../App";

export const alchemyData: Question[] = [
    {
        "question": "What is the central theme of 'Alchemy of Souls'?",
        "options": ["Alchemy and magic", "Time travel", "Political intrigue", "Romance and drama"],
        "answer": "Alchemy and magic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist in the series?",
        "options": ["Jang Uk", "Naksu", "Mu-deok", "Seo Yul"],
        "answer": "Jang Uk"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Naksuâ€™s main goal in the series?",
        "options": ["Revenge", "Finding a lost artifact", "Restoring her powers", "Gaining political power"],
        "answer": "Restoring her powers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is a skilled mage and also the love interest of Jang Uk?",
        "options": ["Mu-deok", "Naksu", "Seo Yul", "Park Dang-gu"],
        "answer": "Mu-deok"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the powerful magical item that plays a crucial role in the series?",
        "options": ["The Soul Shard", "The Philosopher's Stone", "The Alchemist's Ring", "The Moonlight Pearl"],
        "answer": "The Moonlight Pearl"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is known for his skills in martial arts and magic, and becomes a mentor to Jang Uk?",
        "options": ["Seo Yul", "Park Dang-gu", "Heo Yeom", "Choi Jung-won"],
        "answer": "Heo Yeom"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Jang Uk seek to achieve throughout the series?",
        "options": ["Mastery of alchemy", "Vengeance against enemies", "Finding his true identity", "Restoring his family's honor"],
        "answer": "Restoring his family's honor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the rival faction that poses a significant threat to Jang Uk and his allies?",
        "options": ["The Black Mage", "The Dark Sorcerer", "The Shadow King", "The Grand Alchemist"],
        "answer": "The Black Mage"
    },
    {
        "question": "What magical ability does Mu-deok possess that is central to the plot?",
        "options": ["Shape-shifting", "Teleportation", "Elemental control", "Soul swapping"],
        "answer": "Soul swapping"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary setting of 'Alchemy of Souls'?",
        "options": ["A mystical kingdom", "A modern city", "An ancient temple", "A hidden village"],
        "answer": "A mystical kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is known for their involvement in political machinations and hidden agendas?",
        "options": ["Seo Yul", "Naksu", "Jang Uk", "The Royal Advisor"],
        "answer": "The Royal Advisor"
    }
]
    ;